<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MuseumApp</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Museums of Budapest</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">someemail@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>


    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="museum_of_illusions">Museum of Illusions</string>
    <string name="national_gallery">National Gallery</string>
    <string name="mucsarnok">Műcsarnok</string>
    <string name="mai_mano_house">Mai Manó House</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="large_text">

        "Enter the fascinating world of illusions that will trick your reliance on your senses,but also amaze you at the same time; the world that will confuse you completely, but also educate you\u2026 Visit us and you will be thrilled because nothing is what it seems, especially not in HERE!\n\nAre you ready for even a bigger, better, and more fascinating adventure? Here at the Museum of Illusions in Budapest we offer you an intriguing visual, sensory and educational experience with a handful of new, unexplored illusions."

        "\n\n The Museum of Illusions in Budapest provides you with a space suitable both for social and entertaining tours through the world of illusions, prone to delight all generations."

        "\n\n It is a perfect place to gain new experiences and have fun with friends and family. Not only is it a place for children who love paying it a visit, but it is also a place for parents, grandparents and couples."

        "\n\n Be brave enough to jump into an illusion created by the Vortex Tunnel that will drive you crazy and make stepping forward through a rotating cylinder seem as a great struggle and yet the surface is so stable and flat! Deform the image of yourself in the Mirror Room, lose yourself in the Infinity room, resist the laws of gravity and size ratio, and take pictures of yourself in EVERY POSSIBLE POSE!"

        "\n\n Enjoy in our collection of holograms, look closer at every optical illusion and thoroughly observe each installation. They are such a brilliant, playful reminder that our assumptions about the world we perceive are often nothing but a specter of illusions.\n If you are told that you will remain speechless faced with such an exhibition, would you believe it?\n \n Every corner of the Museum of Illusions is accompanied by a rational and scientific explanation that allows you to learn a whole lot of extraordinary things about our vision, our perception and the functioning of our intellect. The goal is to discover why our eyes perceive things that are incomprehensible to our brain."

        "\n\n Make sure you visit our playroom with intriguing and educational games and puzzles. These brain bashers are definitely great fun but they also tend to be frustrating.\n\nCome and explore the world of illusions! Experience the impossible! Make sure your camera is fully charged and that there is enough memory space before you visit. By all means, take your camera with you."


    </string>

    <string name="national_gallery_text">

        "The history of the Royal Palace in the Buda Castle, which was at that time recognised as a magnificent royal residence in Europe, dates back to the 14th century, the reign of kings Louis the Great, Sigismund, and Matthias Corvinus (1458–1490). The state of the building badly deteriorated during the Turkish occupation starting in 1541, and during the Battle of Buda in 1686. The restoration, in the then fashionable Baroque style, began during the reign of Queen Maria Theresa in 1749. "

        "\n\n  At the end of the 19th century the palace was expanded with another wing according to the plans of architects Miklós Ybl and Alajos Hauszmann, and later neo-Baroque ornamentation was also added. During World War II the building was again severely damaged; its reconstruction began in the 1960s. The Hungarian National Gallery moved to the Royal Palace of Buda Castle in 1975."

        "\n\n The Hungarian National Gallery is the largest public collection documenting and presenting the rise and development of the fine arts in Hungary. It has operated as an independent institution since 1957. The HNG moved to its present location, the former Royal Palace of Buda, in 1975."

        "\n\n The Buda Palace with its characteristic Dome, easily recognizable even from afar is one of the symbols of Budapest. As the highest point of the Palace, the Dome of the Hungarian National Gallery offers an unparalleled view on the capital."

        "\n\n The family crypt in Buda Castle holding the earthly remains of Archduke Joseph, Palatine of Hungary, his family members and descendants, is the only part of the Hungarian National Gallery that still preserves something of the palace’s original, 19th-century beauty. The crypt was part of and located under the Saint Sigismund chapel, which was demolished in 1961. From the 1790s the palace became the residence of the palatine, i.e. the prevailing Hungarian representative of the king. Archduke Joseph, a brother of King Francis I, held the title of palatine between 1795 and 1847 and, with royal consent, was the first to have the crypts of the castle chapel converted into a family burial place. After the death of the palatine and his widow their son, Joseph Karl, commissioned two architects, first Miklós Ybl and later Alajos Hausmann, to reconstruct the crypt, while the sculptor, György Zala, was entrusted with making the palatine’s sepulchre."

        "\n\n Make sure you visit our playroom with intriguing and educational games and puzzles. These brain bashers are definitely great fun but they also tend to be frustrating.\n\nCome and explore the world of illusions! Experience the impossible! Make sure your camera is fully charged and that there is enough memory space before you visit. By all means, take your camera with you."


    </string>

    <string name="mucsarnok_text">

        "Ever since its establishment at the end of the 19th century, Kunsthalle has been the centre of contemporary Hungarian fine art, and a key institution in canon-formation. It is a national institution with the mission of exhibiting the most significant trends of both contemporary Hungarian and international fine art in Budapest."

        "\n\n The art centre at Heroes’ Square in Budapest is open to the whole spectrum of Hungarian visual culture. It operates strictly according to the principle of aesthetic value, without any constraint of ideology or age. Besides organising exhibitions, programs involving other art forms, and academic conferences, Kunsthalle’s publishing activity is significant as well."

        "\n\n The Műcsarnok (“art hall”) was founded in 1877 on the initiative of the Hungarian National Fine Arts Association. The original building was situated at 69–71 Andrássy Street, now home to the University of Fine Arts. The exhibition hall on Heroes’ Square was erected in 1896 for the millennium celebrations, and was designed by Albert Schikedanz. Today the hall operates on the pattern of the German Kunsthalle: it is an institution run by artists that does not maintain its own collection. The three-bayed, semi-circular apse houses a roofed exhibition hall that allows in light through the roof. Since the building was renovated in 1995 the Műcsarnok has welcomed visitors and leading Hungarian and international contemporary artists alike, mediating and representing modern artistic tendencies whilst not maintaining its own permanent collection."

    </string>

    <string name="mai_mano_house_text">

        "Mai Manó, Imperial and Royal Court Photographer (1855-1917) had his eight-story studio-house and home built in fourteen months in 1893-94."

        "\n\n A professional photographer and specialist, in his time he was one of the best specialists of child portraits. His status in the professional community of that time is uncontested. He was also the founder and editor of the periodical called A Fény (The Light, launched in 1906) The building’s richly decorated neo-renaissance façade clearly served ideological purposes: Mai Manó wanted to lend a past to the young trade, hardly considered to be a form of art by anyone at that time. Take the majolica putti between the ground floor and the mezzanine or the façade paintings on the third floor showing the “six muses of photography”."

        "\n\n Actual photographing took place in the Sunlight-studio on the second floor, we restored in 1996-97. During the restoration, we found the original frescoes hiding bethind the white wallpaper for decades. These used to serve as background for Mai’s portraits. His studio worked in the house for four decades, until 1931. It was followed by a luxury-bar, Arizona, which was closed in 1944."

        "\n\n After the Second World War, a number of institutions and companies moved into the house and a few private apartments were separated as well. In spite of all the vicissitudes, the house kept its original character. It was declared a piece of national heritage in 1996 considering its special architecture, ornaments and industry-historical significance. While the idea to turn the House into a centre of photography resurfaced countless times throughout the decades, the plan’s realization waited for the perseverance and hard work of three zealous persons: Magdolna Kolta, Károly Kincses, and András Bánkuti. Hungarian House of Photography, or as its friends call it, Mai Manó House open since November, 1998. The reconstruction of the building – has been sponsored by the Hungarian State and planned by Szántó and Mikó Architects – is not far from completion."

        "\n\n Mai Manó House presents its exhibitions on three floors."

        "\n\n On the mezzanine, in Kis Manó Gallery – in the bookshop – we organize small-scale exhibitions, sometimes from the works of debutant photographers."

        "\n\n In the four rooms interconnected on the first floor, we organize thematic shows, group-presentations, retrospective exhibitions of classic masters from home and abroad."

        "\n\n On the second floor, in the rooms next to Mai Manó’s Sunlight studio, the retrospective exhibitions may continue or we present a coherent series of photographs."

        "\n\n Our choices are based on quality, not style, which results in a miscellaneous variety of exhibitions, and a colourful overview of the field of photography. We focus on contemporary, sometimes classic works of art."

        "\n\n The aim of Mai Manó House is to advance the development of Hungarian photography and raise photography’s national prestige as a distinct form of art."
    </string>

    <!-- Preference Titles -->
    <string name="messages_header">Messages</string>
    <string name="sync_header">Sync</string>

    <!-- Messages Preferences -->
    <string name="signature_title">Your signature</string>
    <string name="reply_title">Default reply action</string>

    <!-- Sync Preferences -->
    <string name="sync_title">Sync email periodically</string>
    <string name="attachment_title">Download incoming attachments</string>
    <string name="attachment_summary_on">Automatically download attachments for incoming emails
    </string>
    <string name="attachment_summary_off">Only download attachments when manually requested</string>
</resources>